Contact

joelmalamba2@gmail.com +243819883112 LinkedIn Profile

Top Skills · See all

Management · Business
Strategy · Administration
· Marketing · Accounting ·
Strategic Planning · Marketing
Management · Spreadsheets ·
Sales Management · Business
Analysis

Accomplishments · See all

4 Languages · 2 Certifications

Joel Nzoku Malamba

Administrative Assistant at UNION FAIT LA FORCE (U.F.F) Kinshasa

Summary

Reliable assistant marketer involved withStrategist Marketing CampaignCreate new approach to marketMarket research on how to increase clienteleAdministrative work every July or December at a family hotel business. Team player from jobs such as sale agent in MK where I was assigned to work with 2 membersat the Arckermans store Wonder Park withduties of:Customer Care...

Experience

Read more

Administrative Assistant · UNION FAIT LA FORCE (U.F.F)

November 2020 - Present (6 months) · Kinshasa, Congo (DRC)

Retail Sales · Bogart Man

September 2019 - January 2020 (5 months) · Johannesburg Area, South Africa

Sales And Marketing Intern · Pearson Corporate Training

July 2018 - August 2019 (1 year 2 months) · Johannesburg Area, South Africa

Administrative Assistant · Richfield Graduate Institute of Technology July 2016 - August 2016 (2 months) · Pretoria Area, South Africa

Junior Marketing Manager · Flat Hotel MALAMBA

July 2014 - July 2016 (2 years 1 month) · Kinshasa

Education

Richfield Graduate Institute Of Technology

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Marketing/Marketing Management, General · (2015 - 2017)